[
  {
    "question": "In the 1994-95 season, when John Lyall quit as Ipswich Town manager, George Burley replaced him, but from which club did Burley move?",
    "option1": "Ipswich",
    "option2": "Colchester",
    "option3": "Notts County",
    "option4": "Barnet",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "How many clubs based in London played in the first FA premier League in season 1992-93?",
    "option1": "5",
    "option2": "9",
    "option3": "2",
    "option4": "6",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the gifted striker who scored 10 hat tricks plus one five goal effort during his illustrious Premiership career?",
    "option1": "Alan Shearer",
    "option2": "Robbie Fowler",
    "option3": "Thierry Henry",
    "option4": "Ian Wright",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the Premiership's top scorer in 1993/94, the season Manchester United won the league?",
    "option1": "Les Ferdinand",
    "option2": "Andy Cole",
    "option3": "Alan Shearer",
    "option4": "Robbie Fowler",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Formerly Gold Coast, which African country is the birthplace of hard tackling defender or midfielder Michael Essien?",
    "option1": "Cameroon",
    "option2": "Nigeria",
    "option3": "Ghana",
    "option4": "Ivory Coast",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Playing for a team situated in the north east of England, which player finished as top goal scorer in the 1999-2000 season?",
    "option1": "Alan Shearer",
    "option2": "Dwight Yorke",
    "option3": "Andy Cole",
    "option4": "Kevin Phillips",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Shay Given made his international football debut vs. Russia in 1996, for which country?",
    "option1": "Wales",
    "option2": "Scotland",
    "option3": "Republic of Ireland",
    "option4": "Northern Ireland",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Dmitri Kharine played in the Premier League, but which team did he play for?",
    "option1": "Arsenal",
    "option2": "Chelsea",
    "option3": "Tottenham",
    "option4": "Wigan",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Gianfranco Zola joined Chelsea in November 1996 in a transfer from which Italian team?",
    "option1": "Parma",
    "option2": "Emploi",
    "option3": "Napoli",
    "option4": "Sampdoria",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team were the 2001-02 League Champions?",
    "option1": "Liverpool",
    "option2": "Manchester United",
    "option3": "Arsenal",
    "option4": "Newcastle United",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Which club is nicknamed the toffees?",
    "option1": "Derby County",
    "option2": "Middlesbough",
    "option3": "Everton",
    "option4": "West Ham United",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "In which year did the FA Premier League begin?",
    "option1": "1990",
    "option2": "1991",
    "option3": "1992",
    "option4": "1993",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Defender Pablo Zabaleta wears the famous light blue and white stripes of which South American country?",
    "option1": "Peru",
    "option2": "Brazil",
    "option3": "Argentina",
    "option4": "Uruguay",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Brad Friedel made his international debut in 1992 for which country?",
    "option1": "England",
    "option2": "Sweden",
    "option3": "USA",
    "option4": "Canada",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Lud√¨k Miklosko was goalkeeper at which club when the Premier League was first contested in 1992?",
    "option1": "Coventry City",
    "option2": "West Ham United",
    "option3": "Nottingham Forest",
    "option4": "Sheffield Wednesday",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Arsenal footballer was the second highest goal scorer in the 2002-03 season?",
    "option1": "Ashley Cole",
    "option2": "Dennis Bergkamp",
    "option3": "Thierry Henry",
    "option4": "Martin Keown",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Swindon Town first appeared in the Premier League in the 1993-94 season, and faced Sheffield United in the opening fixture. Which player scored Swindon's first ever goal in that League?",
    "option1": "Martin Ling",
    "option2": "Craig Maskell",
    "option3": "Andy Mutch",
    "option4": "John Moncur",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player scored the first ever goal in the Premier League?",
    "option1": "Dwight Yorke (Aston Villa)",
    "option2": "Nigel Clough (Nottingham Forest)",
    "option3": "Brian Deane (Sheffield United)",
    "option4": "Matthew Le Tissier (Southampton)",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Which club finished bottom of the table in the first season of the FA Premier League?",
    "option1": "Aston Villa",
    "option2": "Portsmouth",
    "option3": "Bradford City",
    "option4": "Nottingham Forest",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Which club was the first to score 1,000 goals in the Premiership?",
    "option1": "Chelsea",
    "option2": "Manchester United",
    "option3": "Arsenal",
    "option4": "Tottenham Hotspur",
    "answer": 2
  }
]